<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on</title><link>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:48:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Fermi Paradox</title><link>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/the-fermi-paradox/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:48:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/the-fermi-paradox/</guid><description>A pebble sits on a hill. It is not a very soft pebble, and the hill it is sitting on is fairly small compared to the others around it. The pebble might even be described as coarse. Some parts, perhaps even sharp. This pebble has had no chance to soften over the years due to the planet it resides on having no atmosphere to speak of, and therefore has nothing to erode away at its unpleasant surface.</description></item><item><title>Examples of Post-Humanism</title><link>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/kinds-of-posthumanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 19:31:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/kinds-of-posthumanism/</guid><description>Now that we know what post-humanism is, we can finally figure out what some post-human ideologies might look like under our definition. Remember, the goal of any post-humanist ideology should be to at least shift the &amp;ldquo;starting point for serious moral and philosophical inquiry&amp;rdquo; away from the human, and to something else.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s do this. We are going to explore a few real groups I&amp;rsquo;ve observed to be potentially within this fake version of a real ideology that I made up.</description></item><item><title>What Is Post-Humanism?</title><link>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/what-is-posthumanism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 17:54:41 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://posting-humanism.github.io/posts/what-is-posthumanism/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve read the title, and you see my blog. You keep reading this sentence and you see the following words: &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s, together, go into this ideology with a completely blank slate.&amp;rdquo; You think to yourself &amp;ldquo;you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been needing a new ideology for a bit now&amp;rdquo; and you agree. Together, we both clear our minds. We close our eyes, and we see nothing. We feel nothing. We let the void envelope our senses.</description></item></channel></rss>